A Finding Aid to the Linda Farris Gallery Records, 1969-1995, in the Archives of American Art AAA.lindfarr
Archives of American Art
Linda Farris Gallery records
1969-1995
AAA.lindfarr
Archives of American Art
13.4 Linear feet 13 Boxes, 1 sol, 1 ov folder
The records of Seattle's avant-garde Linda Farris Gallery measure 13.4 linear feet and date from 1969-1995. The bulk of the records consist of artists' and exhibition files. Also found are gallery business correspondence, administrative files, event files, reference files, records of sales, scattered legal files, the personal papers of gallery owner Linda Farris, and printed materials.
Farris, Linda
Linda Farris Gallery.
Scope and Contents note
The records of Seattle's avant-garde Linda Farris Gallery measure 13.4 linear feet and date from 1969-1995. The bulk of the records consist of artists' and exhibition files. Also found are gallery business correspondence, administrative files, event files, reference files, records of sales, scattered legal files, the personal papers of gallery owner Linda Farris, and printed materials. Business correspondence is with galleries, dealers, publishers, museums, and other businesses. Administrative files are varied and include advertising and promotion materials, exhibition schedules, mailing lists, guest books, a scrapbook, and gallery history.
Artists' files are found for many contemporary American artists that interested Linda Farris or were represented by the gallery. The contents of each file vary but many include photographs and slides, writings, correspondence, and printed materials. Files for Lynda Barry, Grisha Brusking, Charles Clough, Ronnie Landfield, Charles Luce, Michael Lucerno, Sherry Markovitz, Louise Nevelson, Barbara Noah, and Beverly Pepper are particularly rich. Exhibition files are for Linda Farris Gallery exhibitions and include printed materials, correspondence, loan and consignment agreements, and photographs.
Event files cover anniversary celebrations, lectures, panel discussions, and receptions. There are 17 sound cassette recordings of "Art Now" lectures and "Focus" panel discussions. Scattered reference files contain collected materials on subjects of interest to the gallery. There are scattered financial, sales, and legal files. Sales records cover 1970-1979.
Linda Farris' personal papers contain printed materials about her and the gallery and other materials concerning her professional and curatorial work outside of the gallery. There is also a transcript of an oral history with Farris and a news interview.
Printed materials include published books and magazines, clippings and exhibition catalogs and announcements.
Photographs are scattered throughout adminstrative files, exhibition files, event files, and Linda Farris' personal papers.
Related Archival Materials note
An oral history interview with Linda Farris conducted in 1975 by Sally Swenson, is located in the University of Washington University Libraries Digital Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The Linda Farris Gallery records were donated to the Archives of American Art by owner Linda Farris in 1995 at the time she closed the gallery.
Conditions Governing Access note
Use of original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center. Use of archival audiovisual recordings with no duplicate access copy requires advance notice.
Biographical/Historical note
The Linda Farris Gallery was Seattle's leading venue for contemporary art during its twenty-five years of operation.
Linda Farris opened Gallery East in Bellevue in 1970, and a year later moved to Pioneer Square in Seattle, changing the name to Linda Farris Gallery in 1973. The gallery continued to present contemporary art there until closing in December 1995. Art dealer Linda Farris began representing a group of promising artists, all graduates of the University of Washington. Greg Kucera of the Greg Kucera Gallery noted in an article for the Seattle Weekly, "Their work could be loosely seen as a movement, complete with aesthetic interrelationships, convenient marriages, an unintelligible manifesto in the form of Dennis Evans' quirky pronouncements…" From the same article he states, "Her avant-garde gallery changed forever the nature of being an art dealer in Seattle." It was among the three or four most influential galleries in the Pacific Northwest.
The gallery held exhibitions of many nationally known contemporary artists, including Sam Francis, Louise Nevelson, and Robert Rauschenberg, as well as Northwest artists Jeffrey Bishop, Dennis Evans, Sherry Markovitz, Nancy Mee, Norie Sato, and Patti Warashina. The latter group started with the gallery and remained loyal at the time of its closing in 1995.
Art dealer, collector and free-lance curator Linda B. Farris (1944-2005), a native of San Francisco and a graduate of the University of California, Berkeley (1966), was an active participant in and style setter for the Seattle art world for the twenty-five years she was in business. As a member of the art community she actively supported the Henry Art Gallery at the University of Washington, Pilchuck Glass School, and Seattle Art Museum's Contemporary Art Council, and served on the boards of directors of Henry Art Gallery and Factory Visual Arts. Farris curated "Eight Seattle Artists" in 1981 for the Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art and "Self Portraits" in 1983 for the Los Angeles Municipal Art Gallery. She also led the movement to keep Henry Moore's "Vertebrae" from leaving Seattle, and instituted a series of talks, panel discussions, performances, and tours in her gallery, and in and around Seattle.
This note draws heavily on the Archives of American Art's West Coast Regional Collector Paul Karlstrom's collection description written upon acquisition of the papers.
Arrangement note
The collection is arranged as 8 series.
Series 1: Correspondence, 1975-1991, undated (Box 1; .7 linear feet)
Series 2: Administrative files, 1970-1995, undated (Box 1-2; 1 linear feet)
Series 3: Artists and Exhibition files, 1969-1995, undated (Box 2-9; 6.6 linear feet)
Series 4: Events files, 1971-1990, undated (Box 9; 0.6 linear feet)
Series 5: Reference files, 1969-1994, undated (Box 9-10; 0.6 linear feet)
Series 6: Financial, Sales and Legal files, 1970-1995 (Box 10; 0.4 linear feet)
Series 7: Linda Farris Papers, 1972-1995 (Box 10-11; .9 linear feet)
Series 8: Printed Materials, 1970-1995 (Box 11-13; 2 linear feet)
Barry, Lynda, 1956-; Bruskin, Grisha, 1945-; Clough, Charles, 1951-; Landfield, Ronnie, 1947-; Luce, Charles, 1947-; Lucero, Michael, 1953-; Markovitz, Sherry; Nevelson, Louise, 1899-1988; Noah, Barbara; Pepper, Beverly; Art galleries, Commercial--Washington (State)--Seattle; Art, Modern--20th century--Washington (State)--Seattle; Art--Washington (State)--Exhibitions; Artists--Northwestern States; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); Interviews; Lectures; Photographs; Scrapbooks; Sound recordings; Transcripts; Visitors books
- Correspondence, 1975-1991, undated; Series 1; 0.7 Linear feet Box 1, Sol 14
  Arrangement note
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of correspondence.
  Scope and Contents note
  General business correspondence is between owner Linda Farris and galleries, dealers, publishers, museums, and other businesses; some with enclosures such as photographs and brochures. Topics covered include orders and payments for art works, invitations and exhibition announcements from other galleries, and general business issues. Additional correspondence is found in other series as well.
  - Current Clients, 1977-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Current Clients, 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Current Clients, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dealers, 1975-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - Dealers and Inventory, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General, 1972-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Museums, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Administrative files, 1970-1995, undated; Series 2; 1 Linear feet Box 1-2
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  Administrative records include advertising and promotion materials, mailing lists, owner's notes, exhibition schedules, forms, corporate leads and information, guest books, gallery history information, including opening, early years and closing, office wall materials (space devoted to arts information on wall of gallery), photographs and slides of the gallery and Linda Farris, and a scrapbook on various artists for client use.
  - Blank forms, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Corporate Leads, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Corporate Notebook Originals, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Exhibitions Out of Gallery, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Exhibition Schedules, 1987, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
  - Gallery and Linda Farris Photographs, 1971-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Gallery and Linda Farris Slides, 1982, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Gallery Closing - Auction, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Gallery Closing - Goodbye, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Gallery East - Early Years, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gallery East First Year, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Guest Book, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Guest Book, 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Invitation Ideas, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Items from Gallery Office Wall, 1973-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mailing Lists, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Messages, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Messages, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Notes - Idea and Project Books, circa 1970s (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Overseas Color Printing - Ruffner et al, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Promotion Booklet, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Materials - Miscellaneous, 1983-1988, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Publicity Promotions, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Reception Invitation, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Rental of Artist Installation Program, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook - for Client Use, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Upcoming Exhibitions Out of Gallery, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Artists and Exhibition files, 1969-1995, undated; Series 3; 6.6 Linear feet Box 2-9, Sol 14, OV 15
  Arranged in two subseries:
  Subseries 1: Named files, 1969-1995, undated
  Subseries 2: Exhibitions files, 1975-1995, undated
  The Artists and Exhibition files contain a wide variety of materials created and collected by Linda Farris Gallery on artists and exhibitions. Artists' files for Lynda Barry, Grisha Brusking, Charles Clough, Ronnie Landfield, Charles Luce, Michael Lucerno, Sherry Markovitz, Louise Nevelson, Barbara Noah, and Beverly Pepper are particularly rich. Notable exhibitions covered include "My Neighbor the Kingdom" with nearly 30 artists participating in an exhibit coordinated with the opening of the stadium, "Self Portraits" with works by 47 artists, including Andy Warhol, Robert Mapplethorpe, and Edvard Munch, and "Eight Seattle Artists" held at the Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art.
  - Artists' Files, 1969-1995, undated; Subseries 3.1
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by surname.
    Artists' files contain a wide variety of materials either created by or collected and collated by Linda Farris Gallery, such as photographs and slides, correspondence, exhibition catalogs, writings, publicity, and price lists.
    - Nicolas Africano "Portraits of Rebecca" (1995) (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Robert Arneson, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Lynda Barry "Naked Ladies"(1984) (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Lynda Barry, 1981-1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Lynda Barry, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Lynda Barry, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Keith Beckley "New Work" (1983) (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Lynda Benglis "Sculpture and Silk Paintings" (1990) (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Billy Al Bengston "Honolulu Watercolors" (1982), 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Jeffrey Bishop "New Paintings" (1982), 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Harry Bowers "Color Photographs" (1978) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Keith Boyle "Collage Drawings" (1973) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Judy Lerner Brice, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Christopher Brown "new drawings, monotypes & prints" (1992), 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Grisha Bruskin "Paintings, Scultures, Prints" (1993), 1988-1993 (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
    - Guy Buffet, 1969, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Marsha Burns, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Christo Javacheff, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Charles Clough "Love Songs / Dance Tunes" (1983) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Charles Clough "New Work" (1981), 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Charles Clough "Recent Paintings" (1980) (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Chema Cobo "New Paintings - Works on Paper" (1984), 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Carolyn Cole, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    - Alison Collins, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Walter Cotten "New Works" (1983) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Ford Crull "New Paintings and Works on Paper" (1988), 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Laddie John Dill "New Paintings, Drawings and Wall Reliefs" (1984), 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Dennis Evans "The Four Forces of the Universe" (1995) (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Dennis Evans "Seven Garments and Seven Lies for the Passing of Days" (1980), 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - John Edwards Rajanen "New Paintings" (1976), 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Tom Fawkes "Paintings Watercolors Constructions" (undated) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Sam Francis "Selected Lithographs Large Scale Etchings" (1989) (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Richard Francisco "New Works" (1983) (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Richard Francisco "Recent Paintings" (1980) (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - Ann Gardner "Familiar Rhythms" (1992), 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Ann Gardner "Positioning" (1995), 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Nancy Genn "Handmade Paper Works" (1978), 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - David Gilhooly, 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Sam Gilliam "paintings, watercolors, prints" (1974), 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Robert Gonzales, 1974-1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Mike Hascall "new paintings & drawings" (1991) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Louise Hoeschen "New Paintings" (undated) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Louise Hoeschen "Recent Paintings" (1987) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Louise Hoeschen "Recent Paintings and Drawings" (1981), 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Tom Holland "New Paintings" (1979) (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Tom Holland "New Works on Paper" (undated), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Harold Hollingsworth "Paintings Drawings Books" (1993) (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Mel Katz "New Sculpture" (1982), 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Mel Katz "Post Series" (1977) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Mel Katz "Selected Works 1972-1980" (1980) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Mel Katz "Wall Works & Paper Pieces" (1975) (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Ronnie Landfield "New Paintings" (1981) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Ronnie Landfield "New Paintings" (1987), 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Ronnie Landfield "New Paintings & Works on Paper" (1984) (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Ronnie Landfield " Recent Paintings" (1979), 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Carolyn Law "Sculptural Installations" (1979), 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Roy Lichtenstein, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Charles Luce "An Exhibition of New Works" (1976), 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Charles Luce "Fans" (1979), 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Charles Luce "Wind Silhouettes and Related Shadow Tales" (1979) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Michael Lucerno "New Sculpture" (1982) (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Michael Lucerno "New Sculture in Bronze" (1987) (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Michael Lucerno "Reclamation Series" (1995) (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Sherry Markovitz "Bucks and Does" (1981), 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Sherry Markovitz "Easy Targets" (1983) (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Sherry Markovitz "Life Forms" (1992) (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Nancy Mee "The Architecture of the Spine" (1982) (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Nancy Mee "New Sculpture" (1990) (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Lawrence Miller "oils & watercolors" (undated) (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Peter Millet "New Paintings" (1981), 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Peter Millet "New Paintings and Drawings" (1983) (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Michael Moore "Paintings" (1974), 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Margaret Moorman "recent Paintings and drawings" (1977) (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Matt Mullican, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Louise Nevelson, 1969-1980 (Box 5, Folder 1-6)
    - Louise Nevelson - Print Portfolio "Celebration" (1980) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Louise Nevelson "Recent Wood Sculpture" (1978) (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Barbara Noah, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Barbara Noah "No Net" (1981) (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Barbara Noah "Recent Works" (1978) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Barbara Noah "Tampering with Evidence" (1979) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Isamu Noguchi, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Kenneth Noland, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Nathan Oliviera "recent works on paper" (1973), 1963-1973 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
    - Andy Ostheimer "Diorama"(1982) (Box 5, Folder 17-18)
    - Mark Ota "Recent Paintings" (1980), 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Gertrude Pacific, 1972-1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Harold Paris, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Beverly Pepper, 1974-1981 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Beverly Pepper, 1974-1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Mary Ann Peters "Silent Partners" (1983), 1978-1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Bob Peterson "Seattle Discovered" (1977) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Richard Pettibone, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Robert Rauschenberg "hand collage and hand silkscreen on paper" (1979), 1976-1985 (Box 6, Folder 5-8)
    - Barbara Rogers "New Paintings and Works on Paper" (1976), 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
    - Betye Saar, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Peter Santino "Recent Work" (1983), 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Norie Sato "Peripheral Vision and Other New Work" (1983) (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Norie Sato "Image Decay" (1981) "Machine Memory" (1995) "Incidents of Interference" (1987), 1981, 1987, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Italo Scanga "New Sculpture and Works on Paper" (1986), 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Barbara Schwartz "New Works" (1982), 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
    - Patrick Siler "Paintings" (1984) (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Julie Speidel "Bronze Sculpture" (1987) "Bronze Sculpture" (1990) "Open Ground" (1994), 1987-1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Kim Steele, 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Bruce Pitcairn Strachan, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Merrily Tompkins "El Nino" (1987), 1984-1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Andy Warhol "Ten Portraits of Jews of the Twentieth Century" (1980), 1980-1985 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Dan Webb "Without a Sound" (1995), 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - William Wiley, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Bing Wright, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition files, 1975-1995, undated; Subseries 3.2
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by title.
    Exhibition files are for Linda Farris Gallery exhibitions and include announcements, brochures, clippings, correspondence, loan and consignment agreements, notes, press releases, price lists, posters, photographic materials, and background material. The amount of material varies widely from file to file.
    - ADAA "The Art Show" (1990), 1986-1990 (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
    - "Artstore" (1993) (1994) (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Billy Al Bengston / Laddie John Dill / Tom Holland / Edward Ruscha: New Works on Paper" (1983) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - "Current" (1986) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "Dangling Dualities" (1979), 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - "Dennis Evans / Ubu Waugh: Instruments and Diagrams" (1978) (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - "Drawings" (1977) (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - "Eight Seattle Artists" (1980), 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 14-17)
    - "Fiber Structures" (1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - "Furniture by Architects" (1987) (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - "I'm Not Really a Realist Realism Show" (1976) (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "Images of Women" (1975) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - "In Touch" (1976) (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "Introduction '75 Charles Luce Matt Glavin" (1975) (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Keith Beckley Jeffrey Bishop Norie Sato, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - "Linda Farris at Blackfish" (1982) (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - "Linda Farris Selects: California" (undated) (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - "My Neighbor the Kingdome" (1976) (Box 7, Folder 27-29)
    - "My Neighbor the Kingdome" (1976) (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - "Lawrence Miller / Lee Loveland" (1975) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - "Louise Hoeschen paintings and drawings / Leslie McKay Johnson American Collectibles Series: The Fiesta Miniature" (undated) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "Microsoft Art Exhibits" (1987) (1988) (1989), 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Exhibitions", 1973-1995 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
    - "New Ideas" (1978) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - "New Paintings" (1986) (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - "New York / New Work" (1989), 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
    - "1979" (1979) (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
    - "Nola Ahola Coallges, Watercolors, Textiles / Maria Winkler Green Photo Transfer Drawings" (undated) (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - "A Personal Veiw: Three Decades of Linda Farris Gallery" (1995) (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - "Print Project" (1982), 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - "Print Show" (1977) (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - "Self Portraits" (1983) (Box 8, Folder 18-23)
    - "Sherry Markovitz / Judy Lerner Brice / Louise Hoeschen" (undated) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - "3.2.1" (1980) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - "Three Young Artists" (1979) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - "X-Change: 5 L.A. Artists - 5 Seattle Artists" (1983), 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - "Yours, Mine and Ours: Glass Sculpture and Chandeliers by Ginny Ruffner, Paintings by Steve Kursh" (1995) (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Events files, 1971-1990, undated; Series 4; 0.6 Linear feet Box 9
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by event type.
  Events included anniversary celebrations, lectures and panel discussions, and receptions. Panel discussion series include "Conversations" as part of the Goodwill Arts Festival, "Focus I" and "Focus II." The "Farris Wheel" was a series of lectures, discussions and tours. Included in these records are 17 sound cassettes including recordings of "Art Now" lectures and "Focus" panel discussions, three are unlabeled and one is illegible. There is also Seattle's mayor's proclamation of January 7, 1985 as Linda Farris Day, found in the fifteenth anniversary file.
  - Farris Wheel - Notes and Brochures, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Fifteenth Anniversary file, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Lectures - Art Now, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lectures - Office Wall, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Lectures and Panels, 1978, undated; 7 Sound cassettes (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Lectures and panels presumably held at the gallery including Minimal Art/Post Painterly Abstraction, Panel Art of the 70s, Art Now Assemblage, Abstract Expressionism Lecture II.
  - Focus Panel Discussions, 1979, undated; 7 Sound cassettes (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Focus panel discussions, possibly 2 copies of each, some spanning multiple tapes: The Galleries, The Critics, The Artists, The Collectors.
  - Unmarked Sound Cassettes, undated; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Unlabeled, appear to be related to other groups of sound cassettes above, possibly copies of lectures.
  - Miscellaneous Events, 1973-1982, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ninth Anniversary, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Panel Discussions - Focus, 1973, undated (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  - Panel Discussions - Focus II, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
  - Panel Discussions - Goodwill Games - Conversations, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Panel Discussion - Media Coverage of the Arts, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Panel Discussion - What's This New Art All About Anyway?, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Reception - Northwest Artists, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)